JAY TSENG

empowering through design & media

JAYTSENG.COM JAYT@SFU.CA (604) 764 0568

1626 BLUEJAY PLACE COQUITLAM, BC

about

Born in Taipei, Taiwan and initially studying engineering, I am an amalgamation of multiple disciplines and cultures. Now as a student of design & media at School of Interactive Arts & Technology in Canada, I strive to integrate excellent user centric design elements into my

technical projects, while bringing the technical knowledge into my design projects. I enjoy being challenged with wicked problems and my passion is enabling human and technological interactions through design as well as empowering people through storytelling and audio visual experiences.

skills

$-\star\star\star$

ADOBE SUITE

Premiere Pro, After Effects, Illustrator, Indesign, Audition

PHYSICAL MAKING

Wood & Plastic shop tools, Technical design & drawing, 3D Prototyping & Printing

ELECTRIC CIRCUITS

Circuit Prototyping & Testing, PCB Assembly

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

C/C++, HTML + CSS3 + JS

OTHER SOFTWARE

Microsoft Office Suite, Sketchup + VRay, Solidworks, Maya

$-\star\star$

ADOBE SUITE

Adobe XD, Photoshop

ELECTRIC CIRCUITS

Electric Circuit Design

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Java, Python

DIGITAL PROTOTYPING

Adobe XD, AxrureRP, Sketch

OTHER SOFTWARE

Matlab, Rhino + Grasshopper

—**★**

PHYSICAL MAKING

CNC Routing

why hire me?

EMPLOYMENT

_space MAKERSPACE SFU 2017-2018

lead the creation of a 1350sqft. space at SFU

SIMON FRASER UNIV. IAT 202 TA 2016- now

prepare & lead up to three labs of 24 students

PICTURE PROSE / STREAM PROD. 2014-now

creative agency, director, camera operator, editor

JC IMAGES / LION FRAME STUDIO 2012-now

glidecam operator, crew chief for wedding video

GRAND BEAR MEDIA 2014-2016

logistics coordinator, glidecam op. for tv show

PASSION PROJECTS

CREATIVE PROBLEM SOLVING SOCIETY 2010- now

board of directors (to 2015), ceremony director

ELVA PROJECT with LH PRODUCTION 2016-2017

director & cinematographer for video series

STRENGTHS & INTERESTS

emphasize experience in all design & media element great interest in Internet of Things and electronics avid reader of technology blogs and news creative, critical, & passionate about tech & design

confident in public speaking & communication experienced in teamwork, management, & orgnazation independent, cooperative, responsible, & trustworthy

EDUCATION

SIMON FRASER UNIVERSITY

5th Year - School of Interactive Arts and Technology

PORT MOODY SECONDARY

International Baccalaureate (IB) Diploma Graduate

TECHNICAL DESIGN

2015 KUELII SMART DESIGN

to - founder & ceo. lead in mechanical & experience design

- designed intelligent IOT fan solution for space cooling

2017 IAT 481: BUSINESS OF DESIGN

- electrical design, technical design, & manufacturing
- entrance information experience via digital & physical solution

2016 IAT 336: MATERIALS IN DESIGN

- team lead in electrical design, technical design & manufacturing
- designed & assembled lamp of glass, paper, and metal

2014 WESTERN ENGINEERING COMPETITION

- represented SFU @ WEC 2014 in Edmonton, AB
- designed mechanical fruit catcher & flood prevention system

EXPERIENCE & MEDIA

2017 MUSEUM OF VANCOUVER: HAIDA NOW

- telling the story of reconcilliation and the urban Haida experience through artists Corey Bulpitt, and MOV curator Kwiaahwah Jones

2016 BUGGIE DELIVERY INC.

- chief strategy officer, senior experience designer

- creating an on call product delivery service

2015 SURREY PARKIT DESIGN CHALLENGE

- achieved 2nd runner up placing result
- designed urban square experience integrating two pianos